<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Product on Yihan&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://yhannahl.github.io/en/tags/product/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Product on Yihan&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:32:24 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yhannahl.github.io/en/tags/product/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FamiPie 🎈</title>
      <link>https://yhannahl.github.io/en/projects/famipie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:32:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yhannahl.github.io/en/projects/famipie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;famipie-派家&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;FamiPie 派家&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;---a-rapid-response-housing-product-for-the-aftermath-of-an-earthquake&#34;&gt;&amp;ndash; A rapid response housing product for the aftermath of an earthquake.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[ &lt;em&gt;FamiPie is a modular air film placement space for PTSD patients after the earthquake. Fami refers to family, representing family; Pie is a description of the appearance of the product.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;By using a membrane instead of a hard ceiling, PTSD patients are liberated from the worries of &amp;ldquo;the disaster of extinction&amp;rdquo;, even if it collapses, it will not hurt people at all; by using arc language, subvert the square style of traditional buildings, let The patient enters the unique past environment, quickly escapes from the aftermath of the disaster, and accelerates forgetting the trauma; the two hard plates are like open books, forming a stable triangle. FamiPie expands according to the size of the family to ensure sufficient living space for the individual; realizes regional division through modules and no longer feels &amp;ldquo;placed&amp;rdquo;; through the formation of settlements, families can help each other to overcome difficulties together. At the same time, the arc shape makes the arrangement style no longer like a private soldier fighting like a slab house, but rich in layers, with no end in sight at a glance.&lt;/em&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dora Bird Feeder 🕊️</title>
      <link>https://yhannahl.github.io/en/projects/dora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 23:28:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yhannahl.github.io/en/projects/dora/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;dora-bird-feeder-鸟类喂食器&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Dora Bird Feeder 鸟类喂食器&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;---an-upcycling-product&#34;&gt;&amp;ndash; An Upcycling Product.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[ &lt;em&gt;Dora is a bird feeder made from recycled square packaging gift boxes. The material handling method reduces energy waste as much as possible, and the recycled gift box is assembled with 3D printed accessories that can be used for a long time to continue the use value of the composite paper itself. In terms of styling and decoration, the combination of rattan patterns enhances the decoration, and at the same time increases the possibility of interaction between the bird and the product, thus bringing a richer experience to the observer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The overall purpose of the project is to create a story between humans and natural creatures by enhancing the friendly interaction between humans and natural animals, and to convey the value of sustainable and harmonious development to the society.&lt;/em&gt; ]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
